malikscruggs93@gmail.com (510) 754-7631 9311 Olive st. Apt. C, CA 94603

Malik Scruggs

Data entry and analytics is the field I've been in for the last 2 years. I've had 2 years of building and testing electric/autonomous vehicle. Alos, I've had

10 years experience troubleshooting and repairing computers of various people I know I'm a very motivated individual who works hard and is very easy to work with. I'm excellent with people and technology alike!

EXPERIENCE

<u>Capture Technologies, Oakland, CA—Service tech</u> June 2019 - Present

- Establish network in businesses
- Monitor networks in businesses
- Install/troubleshoot access control (card readers and cameras)
- Troubleshoot computers on network
- Configure software for access control

Cruise GM, San Fransisco, CA — Autonomous Vehicle Trainer July 2018 - June 2019

- Data entry for autonomous vehicle using various programs simultaneously
- TroubleShooting on board computer and programs to allow vehicle tooperate
- Analyzing data using various programs while vehicle drives autonomously while actively observing surroundings for safety hazards
- Offering full reports to engineering team to help perfect the system
- Train new employees on autonomous vehicle

Frito Lay, Alameda, CA — Material Handler/IT March 2018 - July 2018

- Troubleshoot Both Laser and Thermal Printer
- Enter data to correctly send packages of chips to correct routes
- Physically Load Orders on trucks for distribution

<u>Tesla Motors, Fremont/Palo Alto, CA — Autopilot Data Labeling Tech / Production Associate</u> <u>June 2015 - March 2018</u>

- Annotating geographical landmarks
- Teach autopilot system how to correct interventions
- Using multiple programs to assist engineers perfect autopilot
- Data entry and analytics using various programs
- Building the very first Model 3's (installing brakes, seats, windows, tires, wiring and batteries
- Building Model S and Model X

EDUCATION

Castro Valley High School - Diploma August 2007 - July 2011, Castro Valley, CA